

Lalit Sanjay Wagh

Software Developer

My Contact

+91 8007073722

Pune, Maharashtra, India

Hard Skill

- Partnerships Management
- Product Management
- Team Management
- · Content Management
- Relationship management
- Communication

Soft Skill

- Business management
- · Business Growth
- · Problem Solving
- Business Operations
- Customer-centric Thinking

Education Background

CDAC Acts Pune

Post Graduation Diploma in Advanced Computing (PG_DAC)

Completed in August 2024

Percentage: 56.7%

VIT-Bhopal University

B.Tech in Computer Science(Specialisation in Gaming Technology)

Completed in 2022

CGPA: 7.38

HSE BOARD

12th standard Completed in 2018

Percentage: 72%

About Me

I am an engineering graduate with a Post Graduate Diploma in Advanced Computing (CDAC). My background in technology and business, combined with hands-on project experience, equips me with a unique blend of technical and entrepreneurial skills.

Professional Experience

Good Health Company

27th March 2023 - 28th June 2023

- Handled the position of Affiliate Marketing EIR.
- Generated weekly revenue worth Rs.2,00,000
- Built relationships with influencers
- Generated revenue through 10 additional channels
- Generated 100 orders per day from Influencer's marketing
- Managed 10 different channels for affiliate marketing

DEMLEA

24th September 2022 - 1st January 2023 (Internship)

- Handled the position of Entrepreneur in Residence.
- Content Management
- · Conducted workshop for kids
- Generated revenue for 1st time
- Hired new mentors for the platformGenerated average views of 2k for content

CattleGuru

15th June 2022 - 15th August 2022 (Internship)

- Handled the position of Entrepreneur in Residence.
- Managed the content creation team of 3.
- Created standard and quality templates for all social media platform
- An educational standards video in a fun and professional way.

ServiLaun

1st December 2021 - 28th April 2022

- Built the Laundry Marketplace
- Handled Social Media
- Handled operations
- Consumer-facing responsibility
- 100% contentment of users
- 0 to 1 built of Marketplace
- Marketplace deployment on all platforms
- 100% Accuracy
- 100% Trust relationship with users
- · 5+ stores strategic partnership from the test area

Achievements

2021 – 2022 Built and generated revenue worth Rs.10,000 during my first month of ServiLaun